questions = [
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "We _______ going to the store.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "will", "does"],
        "correct_answer": "are",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "She _______ coffee every morning.",
        "options": ["drink", "drinks", "drinking", "drank"],
        "correct_answer": "drinks",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "Rain pours from the dark clouds.",
        "question": "What's happening in the sky?",
        "options": ["It is sunny.", "It is raining.", "Birds are flying.", "There is a rainbow."],
        "correct_answer": "It is raining.",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "She's the person _______ assisted me yesterday.",
        "options": ["who", "which", "where", "when", "why"],
        "correct_answer": "who",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A2"
    },
    {
        "text": "Rudolpho left in a hurry, clearly annoyed.",
        "question": "How did Rudolpho feel?",
        "options": ["Happy", "Excited", "Angry", "Calm", "worried", "despairing", "pleased"],
        "correct_answer": "Angry",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "These shoes are _______ expensive for me.",
        "options": ["too", "to", "two", "so", "much", "far"],
        "correct_answer": "too",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "The cat rests beneath the table.",
        "question": "Where is the cat?",
        "options": ["On top of the table.", "Above it", "Beside it.", "Below it.", "Behind it."],
        "correct_answer": "Below it.",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "She _______ to the party last night.",
        "options": ["go", "going", "went", "goes"],
        "correct_answer": "went",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "Anna and Elsa have known each other for a long time and have many shared experiences.",
        "question": "What can be inferred about Anna and Elsa's relationship?",
        "options": ["They just met.", "They are strangers.", "They have a history together.", "They are enemies."],
        "correct_answer": "They have a history together.",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "The castle stood tall on the hill, its towers touching the sky.",
        "question": "Where was the castle located?",
        "options": ["By the river", "In the forest", "On a hill", "In a valley"],
        "correct_answer": "On a hill",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "It's very cold outside, so please wear a _______.",
        "options": ["sandwich", "shoe", "t-shirt", "scarf", "lamp", "chair"],
        "correct_answer": "scarf",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "I can't find my keys! I think I _______ them.",
        "options": ["found", "slipped", "lost", "think", "misconstrued", "swam", "climbed", "drew"],
        "correct_answer": "lost",
        "weight": 2,
        "level": "A2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Yesterday, he __________ a new iPad at the store.",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "bought",
        "weight": 2,
        "level": "A2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "She always drinks her coffee with _______.",
        "options": ["sugar", "pepper", "soap", "pencil", "salt"],
        "correct_answer": "sugar",
        "weight": 1,
        "level": "A2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "If I __________ to go to the supermarket, I would buy you as many oranges as you'd like.",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "were",
        "weight": 3,
        "level": "B1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "He enjoys __________ to classical music in his free time. (to listen)",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "listening",
        "weight": 2,
        "level": "B1"
    },

    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Despite the heavy rain, they __________ to the picnic. (to go)",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "went",
        "weight": 2,
        "level": "B1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Another word for a strong fear is:",
        "options": ["rage", "apprehension", "worry", "concern", "terror", "sadness", "misery", "sadness"],
        "correct_answer": "terror",
        "weight": 2,
        "level": "B1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "The best synonym for 'enormous' is:",
        "options": ["tiny", "massive", "weak", "thin", "short", "large", "great", "impressive", "wild"],
        "correct_answer": "massive",
        "weight": 3,
        "level": "B1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Something that is not complicated and easy to understand is:",
        "options": ["complex", "simple", "difficult", "hard", "tough", "okay", "comprehensible"],
        "correct_answer": "simple",
        "weight": 3,
        "level": "B1"
    },
    # ...

    # B2 Level Questions
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Given the severity of the symptoms, you absolutely _______ see a doctor immediately.",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "must",
        "weight": 4,
        "level": "B2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Rarely _______ such a well-crafted student essay. (to see)",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "have we seen",
        "weight": 4,
        "level": "B2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Someone who is willing to take risks: 'adv_______us'",
        "correct_answer": "adventurous",
        "weight": 4,
        "level": "B2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Complete the word for 'infrequently': 'sel___'",
        "correct_answer": "seldom",
        "weight": 4,
        "level": "B2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "We saw a pack of _____ chasing a deer in the woods",
        "correct_answer": "wolves",
        "weight": 4,
        "level": "B2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "If _______ we were exchanging gifts, they would have bought something. (to know)",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "they had known",
        "weight": 3,
        "level": "B2"
    },
    # ...

    # C1 Level Questions
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Had I known about his arrival, I __________ at the airport to receive him. (to be)",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "would have been",
        "weight": 5,
        "level": "C1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Fill in the rest of the letters for this antonym of 'prosperity': 'adv______y'",
        "correct_answer": "adversity",
        "weight": 5,
        "level": "C1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Complete the word for a deep understanding: 'co_______d'",
        "correct_answer": "comprehend",
        "weight": 5,
        "level": "C1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Egypt boasts many attractions, __ _____ the Acropylis is just one (two words)",
        "correct_answer": "of which",
        "weight": 5,
        "level": "C1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "This is the author __________ latest novel has won several awards.",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "whose",
        "weight": 5,
        "level": "C1"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "The boy __ ____ I lent my pen was very bright (two words",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "to whom",
        "weight": 5,
        "level": "C1"
    },
    # ...

    # C2 Level Questions
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "The lecture was so intricate that it __________ only be understood by experts in the field.",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "could",
        "weight": 6,
        "level": "C2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "The combined adventures of Odysseus compose one of the great e____ of Western literature",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "epics",
        "weight": 6,
        "level": "C2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "I got 100% on the test; it was a real ______ (synonym for light wind)",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "breeze",
        "weight": 6,
        "level": "C2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "A bird in the hand is worth two in the ____",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "bush",
        "weight": 6,
        "level": "C2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "A synonym for apathetic: ind_______t",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "indifferent",
        "weight": 6,
        "level": "C2"
    },
    {
        "text": "",
        "question": "Not only __________ submit the application on time, but he also ensured it was error-free.",
        "options": [],
        "correct_answer": "did he",
        "weight": 6,
        "level": "C2"
    },
]
